moshowapp.com 2019-03-31

# MoShow - Privacy Policy

**MOSHOW – SLIDESHOW MOVIE MAKER**

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Last updated May 24, 2018

PICADELIC (“we” or “us” or “our”) respects the privacy of our users (“user” or “you”). This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you use our mobile application MoShow (the “Application”).   Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. 

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS THE APPLICATION. 

If we make any changes to this policy, we will change the “Last updated” date above. You should periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed of any updates. 

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the third-party online/mobile store from which you install the Application or make payments, including any in-game virtual items, which may also collect and use data about you.  We are not responsible for any of the data collected by any such third party. 

**COLLECTION OF YOUR INFORMATION**

Picadelic does not collect personally identifiable information from our users. We do not ask you to register to use the App or collect your name or e-mail address. All photos and videos remain on your device unless shared by you.  

Depending on your use of the app, the following information may be collected:

**Derivative Data   **

Information our servers automatically collect when you access the Application, such as your native actions that are integral to the Application, including favorites and liking songs or video styles, as well as other interactions with the Application. 

**Mobile Device Access**

To provide App functionality to you, we request access, solely with your permission, to certain features from your mobile device, including your mobile device’s camera, microphone, and storage. If you wish to change our access or permissions, you may do so in your device’s settings.

**Transaction Data**

If you choose to make a purchase in the App, information related to your purchase is collected directly by our platform partners.  We do not collect or store any financial information.  We receive information from our partners confirming the purchase to authorize your use of the app.

**Mobile Device Data**

To provide App functionality and track installations, a random identifier is attributed to your device. Should you uninstall the App, this number is no longer attributed to you.

**Push Notifications**

We may request to send you push notifications regarding the Application and we track the response of users to those notifications. If you wish to opt-out from receiving these types of communications, you may turn them off in your device’s settings.

**USE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

Having accurate information about you permits us to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience. Specifically, we may use information collected about you via the Application to: 

1.         Compile anonymous statistical data and analysis. 

2.         Increase the efficiency and operation of the Application.

3.         Monitor and analyze usage and trends to improve your experience with the Application.

4.         Notify you of updates to the Application.

5.         Offer new products, services, mobile applications, and/or recommendations to you.

6.         Perform other business activities as needed.

**DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We may share information we have collected about you in certain situations. Your information may be disclosed as follows: 

**By Law or to Protect Rights**

If we believe the release of information about you is necessary to respond to legal process, to investigate or remedy potential violations of our policies, or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others, we may share your information as permitted or required by any applicable law, rule, or regulation. 

**Third-Party Service Providers**

Through your use of the app, you may share your information with third parties that perform services for us or on our behalf, including payment processing, data analysis, hosting services, customer service, and marketing assistance. 

**Affiliates**

We may share your information with our affiliates, in which case we will require those affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. Affiliates include our parent company and any subsidiaries, joint venture partners or other companies that we control or that are under common control with us.

**Sale or Bankruptcy**

If we reorganize or sell all or a portion of our assets, undergo a merger, or are acquired by another entity, we may transfer your information to the successor entity.  If we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, your information would be an asset transferred or acquired by a third party.  You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and that the transferee may decline honor commitments we made in this Privacy Policy. 

We are not responsible for the actions of third parties with whom you share personal or sensitive data, and we have no authority to manage or control third-party solicitations.  If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails or other communications from third parties, you are responsible for contacting the third party directly. 

**TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES**

**App Analytics**

We partner with the following third-party vendors to analyze the use of the App, determine the popularity of certain content, and better understand online activity. These services may access device information such as your mobile device model, manufacturer, version of your operating system, country, location, and other actions taken within the App. By accessing the Application, you consent to the collection and use of your information by these third-party vendors. 

**Google Firebase** for user analytics. To learn more about Google’s use of data please visit this page: [https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/)

**Facebook** for user analytics. Facebook’s privacy principals can be viewed here:  [https://www.facebook.com/about/basics/privacy-principles](https://www.facebook.com/about/basics/privacy-principles)

**Microsoft Mobile Center** for user analytics.

**Branch.io** ([https://branch.io/](https://branch.io/)) to create URL Links that direct users to the proper App Store for installation of MoShow and track that behavior. If you clicked on a link to discover MoShow, it is likely via a Branch.io link.

**Third-Party Websites and Apps**

If you choose to share your MoShow video directly with other sites such as Instagram, Twitter or Facebook, you will be asked to login to those sites for authentication. If you choose to do so, MoShow will allow you to share your video directly to those sites. 

Once you have done so, any information you provide to these third parties is not covered by this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of any third parties.

**SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We use administrative, technical, and physical security measures to help protect your personal information.  While we have taken reasonable steps to secure the information you provide to us, please be aware that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse.  Any information disclosed online is vulnerable to interception and misuse by unauthorized parties. Therefore, we cannot guarantee complete security if you provide personal information.

**POLICY FOR CHILDREN**

We do not knowingly solicit information from or market to children under the age of 13. If you become aware of any data we have collected from children under age 13, please contact us using the contact information provided below. 

**OPTIONS REGARDING YOUR INFORMATION**

**Communications**

If you no longer wish to receive communications from us, you may opt-out by changing your push notification platform settings. 

**CONTACT US**

If you have questions or wish to raise a complaint on how we have handled your data, you can contact us at dataprotection@picadelic.com.
